familyguyx.net 2008-03-29

# Family Guy X | Watch, Discuss & Rate on Family Guy Episodes!

This private statement was last updated on November 15, 2007.

**1\. Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms**

Family Guy X (FamilyGuyX.net, 'the site', or 'FGX') is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing FamilyGuyX.net, you acknowledge and fully understand FamilyGuyX.net's Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

**2\. Participating Policies**

FamilyGuyX.net runs as a non-profit, non-commercial commenting system for each family guy episodes. Browsing the site means that you agree to participate in the site and agree that the site does not sell any of the posted details, photos to third party.

**3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

FamilyGuyX.net collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: 

  * Your Internet protocol address.
  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Name of your Internet service provider.
  * Web page you linked to our site from.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.
  * Use of Cookies

FamilyGuyX.net may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

Visitors to our website can browse all the profiles and photos listed without registration.

**4\. Changes to this Statement**

FamilyGuyX.net has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "updated" date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**5\. Contacting Us**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us by emailing us at: contact@familyguyx.net.
